[player 1] ♪ Ready or not, here I come ♪
[player 2] ♪ Ready or not, here I come ♪
[player 3] ♪ Ready or not, here I come ♪
TAG
A GAME WHERE ONE CHASES AND CATCHES OTHERS
[player 1] We used to play tag
all the time as kids.
[player 2] I was always the one
who caught everyone.
Hey, Eunsil.
You can't use wrestling on me!
Wait, this is cheating.
[player 3 laughing playfully]
This is fun.
But this is about survival.
[player 4] I'm so pissed off.
[player 5] The Seeker's playing us.
[player 6] It's just us.
Why can't you talk?
[screams] Please!
[player 7] You can't trust
these damn people.
-[player 8] Are you the Seeker?
-[player 9] Something's off.
-[player 10] Something's off.
-[player 11] I can't trust anyone. Damn.
[Pani Bottle] Damn it. Fuck.
Fuck!
A GAME OF TAG
DEADLY TAG
AN ELIMINATION GAME
WHERE ONLY THE LAST PERSON STANDING WINS
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[player 1 sighs]
[host] Welcome to the "Deadly Tag."
The rules here are simple.
You either chase or be chased.
All your abilities
will become the ultimate power
that lets you dominate the food chain.
Do whatever it takes.
Team up when it serves you best,
make the most calculated betrayals,
and fight your way
to the top of the food chain.
PARK JIMIN, BRAINS & POLITICS
ANNOUNCER
ZZONE, POLITICS
SINGER
GYEONG SUJIN, PHYSICAL
ACTRESS
[Jimin] Wait, they're all women.
This might actually be doable.
Based on appearances alone,
they were all women.
I started thinking about
how I could beat them.
PANI BOTTLE, POLITICS
CONTENT CREATOR, TOP TRAVEL YOUTUBER
SHIN JIEUN, PHYSICAL
TEAM KOREA BEACH VOLLEYBALL PLAYER
YOUN SANGHYUN, PHYSICAL & BRAINS
ACTOR, THEATER MAJOR
[Sanghyun] I took off my blindfold
and saw a woman behind me.
I thought, "This could work."
JANG EUNSIL, PHYSICAL
OLYMPIC WRESTLER, PHYSICAL: ASIA WINNER
KIM DDOLDDOL, POLITICS & BRAINS
CONTENT CREATOR, ENGINEERING GRADUATE
[Ddolddol] I'd never been
blindfolded before.
They locked me up, tied me down,
and wouldn't let me move.
Maybe I shouldn't have come.
LEE JOONSU, PHYSICAL
COLLEGE STUDENT, THEATER MAJOR
HORSEKING, PHYSICAL
FITNESS CONTENT CREATOR, BUSINESS MAJOR
HWANG JAEGYUN, PHYSICAL
RETIRED BASEBALL PLAYER
[Jaegyun] I saw something written in red
in front of me.
I tried hard to figure it out,
but I couldn't wrap my head around it.
[Horseking] When I turned around,
I noticed we were chained together.
I thought I needed to free myself first.
But then...
-[loud explosion]
-Geez!
[Horseking] What the heck?
-[explosion]
-[screams]
[host] The first game begins now.
[multiple explosions]
-[Horseking] What the heck?
-[players screaming]
The rules are simple.
Use any strategy and do whatever it takes
to escape the room
and race to the finish line.
You have 10 minutes.
The last person to arrive
becomes the first elimination candidate.
DEADLY TAG
RESTRICTED AREA
[♪ low, tense music playing]
[Ddolddol] I had to get out of there.
The fire was blazing.
Things were blowing up.
I was really starting to panic.
[Dail] When I felt the heat from the fire,
I was stunned.
YANG DAIL, POLITICS & PHYSICAL
SINGER
When I took off the sack,
I saw the box in front of me.
CLUE BOXES PLACED BEFORE THE PLAYERS
I knew I had to get to that box.
[Dail] He was trying to pull me over
as hard as he could.
I knew we were going
to end up fighting from the get-go.
Still, I've worked out a lot,
so I felt confident.
[chain whirring]
YUK JUNSEO, PHYSICAL
FORMER UDT/SEAL, THE IRON SQUAD S1 WINNER
I have a military background.
And I enjoy physical training,
so I think I'd have an advantage
in any physical challenge.
Wait, Yuk Junseo is here.
He has clearly come prepared.
He's already in combat mode.
[Junseo] I was confident
when it came to using strength.
Yang Dail was behind me
and was stronger than I expected.
So I responded with my strength.
[chain rattling]
[gasps]
[chain clinking]
[chain rattles]
No offense to Pani Bottle,
but I thought I could handle him.
Wow.
[Eunsil] I was the first one
to get the hint.
FIRST, SECOND, THIRD
[host] Get rid of the first.
Cut off the heads of the seconds
and offer them on the altar.
[Junseo] I thought about
what it could mean.
[Dail] I found it really hard.
The first's head...
What did it say?
Something about cutting off a head
and cutting open the second's stomach
to make an offering.
I had no clue what it meant.
I really had no idea.
[Pani Bottle] I checked the hint
inside the box.
The numbers and letters
kind of looked like 10, 20 and 30.
I tried different combinations,
but nothing worked.
I wondered what it could be.
I thought I was prepared, so I was sure
that I'd solve the first puzzle.
But I was stuck.
[Jieun] Since using my brain
isn't really my strong suit,
I've decided to solve things
with my physical strength.
[thudding]
The first's head...
[ZZONE] I felt like
the answer had to be there,
so I read it over and over.
Wait a second.
BEWARE OF YOUR OPPONENT'S LIES
LEAVE YOUR SAFE HAVEN
THE TRUTH IS HIDDEN UNDERNEATH
QUESTION FAKE OBEDIENCE
UNCOVER WHAT'S HIDDEN
THE TRUTH IS HIDDEN UNDERNEATH
There were three lines of messages.
I was sure they had something to do
with the answer.
I tried reading the messages.
When I read the characters
from top to bottom...
it said "under the mask."
UNDER THE MASK
"Under the chair" and "under the pillar."
So I looked under the mask...
and there were numbers.
FIRST, SECOND, THIRD
[host] Get rid of the first.
Cut off the heads of the seconds
and offer them on the altar.
That is the key to your survival.
UNDER THE CHAIR
UNDER THE PILLAR
UNDER THE MASK
[Jimin] I can't let them find out.
I was going to solve it and escape
while no one was watching.
[lock clicking]
[clicks]
But it wouldn't work.
[groans] Seriously.
Come on. 3174...
That's when I started to panic.
That had to be the answer,
but it wasn't working.
It was driving me crazy.
But I might have been entering
the code the wrong way.
It was the other way around.
ENTERED THE CODE THE WRONG WAY
[host] You have three minutes left.
REMAINING TIME
[Jimin] The clock kept ticking.
This is driving me crazy.
What do I do?
[cries]
What am I supposed to do?
[footsteps]
[Jimin] Wait...
Who's that?
[Jimin] Excuse me. Wait.
It's impossible. How did they do it?
[Jimin] I was panicking
since I was completely stuck,
but people kept passing by.
[footsteps approaching]
Excuse me.
When I saw more people pass by,
I started getting really nervous.
How on earth did they get free?
It was tied to the belt,
so I just forced it with my strength.
It was tied down really tight.
I decided to force it open.
I was confident in my physical strength.
[Dail] I had to survive first.
PLAYERS WHO RELY ON PHYSICAL STRENGTH
-[Eunsil] Think it'll work?
-Yes, I think so.
-It's working. Just a little more...
-[Jieun laughing]
-Got it!
-Thank you so much! It's finally off.
-[Eunsil] Pants, pants.
-Okay.
Come on, hurry.
[Dail] You need help?
[♪ playful music plays]
STAGGERS
It's coming off.
I figured I could get it off
by taking my pants off.
[ZZONE] I didn't want to be eliminated
on the first day.
I pulled my belt down.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[Eunsil] This is the Main Hall, right?
It's the Main Hall.
I think it is.
PLAYERS ARRIVE ONE BY ONE
Hello.
Here.
[Sanghyun] After about 10 minutes,
it seemed like everyone had arrived.
[Eunsil] Then, I saw Yuk Junseo,
and I saw the baseball player.
Physical strength-wise, I thought,
"This isn't going to be easy."
I didn't see anyone
who seemed particularly intimidating.
I thought I might be weaker physically,
but I could have a better chance
if there are games that use your brain.
[Joonsu] I didn't want to team up
with Youn Sanghyun,
because his eyes looked suspicious.
Since he's an actor,
he'd be good at acting.
He seemed suspicious.
My ear hurts. Damn it.
Aren't there quite a few people
-who haven't arrived yet?
-Yes.
Only one gets eliminated.
[Sujin] I need to take off
this inner layer.
This won't come off.
[groans]
This is so annoying.
At that point, I wasn't even thinking
about solving the problem.
I just panicked
and started yanking them down
as hard as I could.
I'd do whatever it takes not to be last.
[exhales]
[Sujin] Let's get out of here quickly.
It won't be me.
It shouldn't be me.
-Damn it.
-[Sujin groans] My back hurts so bad.
[ZZONE] I ended up
being the first one to get out.
Seriously, I debated what to do.
It's a survival game, after all.
So should I just go
or help one of them get out?
[♪ tense music playing]
What do I do?
-Do you need help?
-[player breathes]
ZZONE CHOOSES JIMIN
I'll hold onto my pants.
Can you pull it down?
[ZZONE] I think
you've pulled it down well.
Just pull them down. Hold on.
Jimin has experience
being on other reality survival programs.
So I figured I really shouldn't end up
as her enemy.
It's all going to come off.
They're coming off.
It's because I took off my inner layer.
[exhales]
-Wait.
-[ZZONE] Sorry?
-No, no.
-It's way too tight.
Like this. This is way too tight.
[ZZONE] Right?
We can't be last though.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
We really can't be last.
[Sujin] Wow. [sniffles]
They wouldn't let me out.
[exhales]
My back hurts.
[groans]
Jimin and the one on my left
were in a hurry to leave.
I was so annoyed.
[groans]
[exhales] I was so mad that I was like,
"Fine, wait and see who wins in the end."
[mic feedback]
[host] It's time to reveal the results.
In Deadly Tag...
the player who finished last,
in 13th place...
is Gyeong Sujin.
She will not be able to participate
in the first game, the Main Match.
AN EMPTY SEAT
[Eunsil] So this is how it starts.
[Jieun] To be honest,
I was glad I made it through.
[Joonsu] I felt bad for her
but was glad it wasn't me.
It's a survival program, after all.
I have to save myself first.
[host] Now, each player
will enter the Dealer Room
and hand in your prize cards.
AFTER THE FIRST GAME
[Horseking] What is this?
CARDS IN THE MAIN HALL
[Joonsu] What are these?
PRIZE CARDS FOR EVERYONE WHO ESCAPED,
EXCEPT THE PLAYER IN 13TH PLACE
100 MILLION, 80 MILLION WON,
60 MILLION, 40 MILLION, 20 MILLION WON
EXCHANGE THE PRIZE CARDS FOR CASH
IN THE DEALER ROOM
DEPOSIT THE MONEY INTO THE LOCKERS
-[dealer] Hello.
-Hello.
[dealer] Mr. Youn Sanghyun,
please present your prize card.
[Sanghyun] I got
to the Main Hall first, but...
SECOND PLACE: JANG EUNSIL
I was reading the instructions
about the cards,
and then Jang Eunsil
took the 100 million won card
before I did.
So I went ahead and took
the 80 million won one.
[Eunsil] All I could see
was the 100 million won card,
so I grabbed it.
What is this?
[dealer] Please choose one key number
from 1 to 14 and state your choice.
[Sanghyun] I'll go with number nine.
YOUN SANGHYUN: 80 MILLION WON & KEY NO. 9
You have selected key number one.
Ms. Jang Eunsil's prize card
is 100 million won.
I'll go with number eight.
-Number five.
-[dealer] You've picked number five.
Please deposit your personal funds
into the locker.
ALL PLAYERS' FUNDS HAVE BEEN DEPOSITED
[Pani Bottle] Geez, what's going on?
[dealer] Please select a player.
[Ddolddol] What's this?
-[ZZONE] This is driving me nuts.
-[Dail] God damn it.
-[Horseking] This is fun.
-[Sanghyun] It's me, right?
[Joonsu] Hold on, I got betrayed.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[host] To those who survived
the advantage game, congratulations.
Here are the basic rules of Deadly Tag.
Deadly Tag will proceed
with the Death Match...
after the Main Match
and a round of voting.
Players who place last in each Main Match
or those who do not earn
an Elimination Immunity Pass
will be at risk of elimination.
The final Death Match player
will be decided by voting.
The Death Match result
will determine who is eliminated.
The final survivor of Deadly Tag
will receive the grand prize
of 100 million won.
[Junseo] I wanted to win it,
and I know I can.
[Sanghyun] The prize money matters,
but there's also the thrill, the honor,
and the pride that come with winning.
[Dail] My goal? To win.
I'll destroy everybody.
[host] The first Main Match
of Deadly Tag is...
"Cops and Robbers."
C&R.
Wow.
What?
[host] Cops and Robbers
consists of three cops and nine robbers
with each player taking a role.
Cops are split into three roles.
Criminal Investigation,
Violent Crimes, and Narcotics.
Robbers are split into groups of three.
Burglars, Assault Criminals,
and Drug Criminals.
CI will handle Burglars,
Violent Crimes
will handle Assault Criminals,
and Narcotics will handle Drug Criminals.
Players start the game
without knowing each other's identities.
The chase consists of two rounds,
and each round includes
a chase and an interrogation.
Criminals must collect
a set number of clues during the chase,
and if they fail to do so, a regular clue
and a decisive clue about that criminal
will be randomly revealed to all players.
During the chase,
cops can tag up to three criminals.
Tagged criminals are locked up in prison.
There are special roles
hidden among the criminals.
The Good Citizen
helps the cop handling their case
catch the other criminals.
There are two Good Citizens,
with one each
in two of the criminal groups.
The Madman
wants to be caught by the police
and lures their assigned cop
into capturing them.
There is one Madman in the criminal group
without a Good Citizen.
After both chase rounds,
the cops and criminals
will vote to arrest a criminal
and identify a traitor respectively.
Once a cop locks up
both of their assigned criminals,
their mission is complete.
But if a Good Citizen or the Madman
is among them, their mission fails.
If a criminal avoids getting arrested
by their assigned cop...
or if they successfully identify
a Good Citizen or the Madman
in the vote to find traitors,
their mission is complete.
The Good Citizens win if they survive
the criminals' vote to find traitors
and if their assigned cop arrests
the two other criminals on their team.
The Madman wins if they survive
the criminals' vote to find traitors
and if they get arrested
by their assigned cop.
Those who complete their missions
will earn 20 million won
and one Elimination Immunity Pass.
Those who fail their missions
will be subject to an Elimination Vote
to decide two elimination candidates.
What?
[Junseo] This is not easy.
This seems pretty intricate.
-Cops...
-Three cops and nine criminals.
Among the criminals...
There are two Good Citizens
and one Madman.
There's one hidden in each group.
-It's like the game Mafia.
-[ZZONE] Yeah, it feels like that.
The Good Citizens could help the cops out.
Exactly, Good Citizens have to help
to win.
I see.
Catch the criminals
and avoid being voted out.
I think it's the most difficult role.
There's no doubt the cops need
speed and physical strength.
As for these criminals and special roles,
they could still deceive people
if they can put on a good act.
The criminals have to find their clues
and keep them hidden.
So they need to use
their bodies and brains.
I thought observation was the key.
Not just observing the clues
but also observing people.
The most important thing is tackling.
I absolutely knew I had to get physical.
So, I was quite confident.
[host] Now, each player will enter
the Dealer Room one by one
and draw a role card
for the Cops and Robbers game.
[Ddolddol]
I didn't really want to be a cop
because I felt like
the role would involve
a lot of hands-on fighting
and physical clashes.
-Hello.
-Mr. Kim Ddolddol,
please point to one card of your choice.
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[Ddolddol] This one.
[dealer] Mr. Kim Ddolddol,
you are Robber 2.
Also...
you are a Good Citizen.
You need to help the cops
catch the other criminals
and survive the criminals' vote
to find traitors.
[Ddolddol] The moment I drew the card,
I thought it was perfect for me.
Even when I play Mafia,
I'm really good at special roles,
like the shaman.
I'm always good at those roles.
I'll go straight to the police
and sell out the criminals' info.
I'll also figure out
who are the other criminals on my team
and act like I'm not the traitor.
[dealer] Here's your profile card
and notebook.
PROFILE CARDS LIST THE CRIME & CLUES
[all chuckle]
Excuse me, can I ask what you picked?
I'm the one being chased.
I'll run for my life.
Hello.
Mr. Lee Joonsu,
please point to a card of your choice.
[Joonsu] I wanted to be a cop.
Horseking and Yuk Junseo...
Except for those two,
I can catch everyone else.
Mr. Lee Joonsu...
you are Robber 3.
And you are a regular criminal.
[Joonsu] I'm glad I wasn't a Good Citizen
or the Madman.
A regular criminal is simple and nice.
[Pani Bottle] I was hoping to get
either the Good Citizen or the Madman.
I thought the Madman role
would be easier to play.
I figured if I just did my best,
the criminals would identify me.
[Jimin] Since I'm pretty good at acting,
I thought I could do the Madman role.
[dealer] Mr. Pani Bottle...
you are Assault Criminal 1.
You are [bleep].
Ms. Park Jimin, you are Drug Criminal 2.
[Horseking] I'll go with this one.
[dealer] Mr. Horseking...
you are Assault Criminal 2.
You are [bleep].
Mr. Yang Dail, you are [bleep].
Those are your clues?
-Yes.
-I see.
-It includes photos and locations.
-[Dail] I see.
So you have to find and get rid of them?
[host] The chase area is divided
into four sections.
The Hotel,
the Grounds,
the Pool,
and the Annex.
Each criminal
must collect nine physical clues
placed throughout the chase area.
The clues consist
of seven general clues...
and two decisive clues
that easily help identify the criminal.
The criminals can locate the clues
using the provided photos.
FIND THE LOCATIONS IN THE PHOTOS
AND PICK UP THE CLUES
[♪ intriguing music playing]
Wait, they zoomed in way too much.
-How am I supposed to find these?
-You can't show them.
How can I find them?
Are you the Madman?
[all laughing]
[Jieun] Right. [chuckles]
[♪ intriguing music playing]
Be careful.
Yuk Junseo is a cop.
Are you a cop?
Yes.
[♪ powerful music playing]
[Jaegyun] Here comes the UDT.
[Ddolddol groans]
[dealer] Mr. Yuk Junseo...
you are a Violent Crimes cop.
Here's your profile card
and investigation notebook.
This is exactly the scenario in my head
where I really hoped the cops
wouldn't be like someone like him.
[all laugh]
-You're a cop, right?
-[Sanghyun] Are you a cop?
[Jaegyun] It's so easy to tell
who's a cop or robber.
I guess the cops get those notebooks.
[Ddolddol] Cops get notebooks.
AN INVESTIGATION NOTEBOOK
WITH PROFILES OF ALL THE CRIMINALS
[dealer] Mr. Youn Sanghyun,
you are a Criminal Investigation cop.
Okay.
[dealer] Ms. Jang Eunsil...
you are a Narcotics cop.
Okay.
As soon as I got the role,
I thought it was a perfect fit for me.
You need the stamina to pull off the role,
so it was something
I felt confident about.
[Jieun] The cop roles
went to people who fit them.
-[Jimin] I know.
-[Sanghyun] Honestly,
Junseo and Eunsil
are both fit and athletic, so I thought
I got lucky with our team.
And Sanghyun seemed like
someone who's pretty sharp.
As a Good Citizen,
I was very happy with the cops.
CI: SANGHYUN,
VIOLENT CRIMES: JUNSEO, NARCOTICS: EUNSIL
SHIN JIEUN, HWANG JAEGYUN, YANG DAIL:
UNKNOWN
[♪ exciting music playing]
[host] In Cops and Robbers,
here's how the tag system works.
At the start, cops have blue patches,
and criminals wear red patches.
If a cop completely removes
a criminal's patch,
it counts as a tag.
You'll now have 20 minutes
for Round 1 private discussions.
ROUND 1 PRIVATE TALKS FOR CRIMINALS
LOOKING AROUND
CRIMINALS HESITATE TO SAY ANYTHING
-You're a criminal?
-I am.
What kind? Assault?
-What kind?
-Assault or...
Assault?
-[Ddolddol] There are three groups.
-The three groups?
Do we need to reveal that now?
Are you all willing to share your roles?
[chuckles]
Unless you're a Good Citizen
or the Madman,
it's better to share.
[♪ tense music playing]
Do we need to reveal them?
I don't see why...
It's easier to catch traitors if we do.
As a criminal, you have to be prepared
in case you get caught.
After being caught, the way to survive
is to identify the Good Citizens.
And to do that,
we need to know who's on which team,
so we can narrow them down.
-That's true, but--
-If someone hesitates,
they're either a Good Citizen
or the Madman.
[Dail] Even if we get arrested
by the cops,
we can survive as long as we find
the Good Citizen
or the Madman on our teams.
You just need to be good
at finding clues and reading people.
Constantly running away isn't the key.
That could actually backfire too.
If I reveal which team I'm on,
and the Madman happens to be
-on my team...
-Exactly.
If we discuss altogether,
the lies will come out.
We'll end up with a higher number
of criminals if someone lies.
[Ddolddol] He cut me off.
I was so annoyed. [scoffs]
Am I going to get identified by Yang Dail?
-[Horseking] Then, should we share--
-It's easier if we do.
Is that so?
[ZZONE] It could work out, but what if
there's a Good Citizen on our team?
We could be doomed, right?
If I share which team I'm on,
and a Good Citizen tells on me...
Exactly, but Dail wants everyone
to reveal their roles.
[ZZONE] Yeah, I know.
[Pani Bottle] I'm a little confused.
Then, when the cops make an arrest,
do they have to guess
both their role and crime?
-Yes.
-If it's the right role but wrong crime,
-that won't count?
-No.
I think the criminals might be better off
not sharing that information
with each other.
[ZZONE] Because there are Good Citizens.
[Pani Bottle] If they don't get
the crime right,
the cops can't make an arrest.
Sharing makes it easier
for Good Citizens to rat.
That's how I see it too.
We have two rounds anyway.
[Jieun] Let's not share for Round 1.
[Dail] I was so frustrated
to see that happen.
I think this private discussion time
is the first and only opportunity
to figure out
who the Good Citizens are
and who the Madman is
by reading people's subtle hints
and reactions.
But nobody was willing
to share their roles.
Since no one said anything...
I just watched.
[mic feedback]
[host] We will now begin Round 1
of the chase.
[alarm blaring]
ROUND 1 CHASE
Darn it.
[Joonsu] Where do we go?
FIND 4 CLUES AND AVOID ARREST
[Ddolddol] Even with all the clues,
we can't get caught?
-[Joonsu] Right, you can't get caught.
-[ZZONE] Geez, I am scared to death!
-[Jieun] Is this the Pool?
-[Dail] How do we get in?
[Jieun] Beats me. Just go.
THE POOL
[♪ powerful music playing]
[sniffles]
[Pani Bottle] Is it this way?
The dirt pile. Where is it?
There's no time.
I figured I should start with the Pool
since it was the farthest from us.
So I gathered all the pool photos together
and headed there.
What the fuck is this?
YANG DAIL'S PHOTO OF CLUE LOCATION
SEARCHING FOR THE DIRT PILE
THAT MATCHES THE PHOTO
Where is this place?
HOWEVER THE CLUE IS NOWHERE TO BE SEEN
Where is this?
THE POOL AREA IS1,000 PYEONG,
OR 3,300 SQUARE METERS
[ZZONE] Why is the pool so huge?
EVERYTHING IN SIGHT
IS WITHIN THE SEARCH AREA
Fuck, it's supposed to be here.
It's not here on site.
What the heck is this?
[ZZONE] Damn it, where is it?
I'm right here though.
THE ANNEX
You can't find it, can you?
This is the right place.
I know.
It was in the photo
but it wasn't at the place.
Time was ticking,
and the cops were about to come.
And I totally panicked.
THE GROUNDS
What's this? Is this it? No, it's not.
THE POOL
This is all there is.
Is it even here?
-You found one?
-Yes.
What does it look like?
How did you find it?
I looked at the photo.
[exhales]
-How many did you find?
-[Jaegyun] Three.
[Dail] Damn it.
[♪ energetic music playing]
[Jaegyun] I'd already found everything
before the cops came out.
I checked the notebook and the map
to plan out the best route ahead of time.
[beeps]
-[Jimin] You found it?
-Yes.
[beeps]
-[Joonsu] You found one?
-Yes.
[beeps]
I found everything really fast.
I don't get why they can't find
what's in the photos.
[Dail] Damn it,
I looked around here earlier.
A MINUTE BEFORE THE COPS ENTER
I found it. I found it.
I fucking found it.
I found it.
[exhales]
AFTER GETTING USED TO THE AREA,
THEY START FINDING THE CLUES
HORSEKING COLLECTS A CLUE
AND GETS RID OF THE PHOTO
[loud buzzer sounding]
[gasps]
[groans]
STARTLED
Fuck.
[host] Cops may enter the chase area.
COPS AND ROBBERS ROUND 1
[shushes]
YOUN SANGHYUN GOES ALONE
IN A DIFFERENT DIRECTION
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-[Joonsu] What was that?
-They're on their way now.
-The seekers are on the move.
-[Joonsu] Really?
They'll come running.
This is connected to the outside.
Keep your guard up.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
COP SANGHYUN APPEARS
Hey, go that way. That way.
THE CRIMINALS SCRAMBLE AS A COP APPEARS
[Sanghyun] I checked
where the criminals were headed to
before the cops started moving.
[♪ exciting music playing]
EARLIER
[Junseo] As it's a wide area to cover,
I thought it'd be inefficient to move
as a group of three.
I figure it'll take a while
to get familiar with the layout.
-[Eunsil] So we split up?
-For Round 1, yes.
[Sanghyun] I was in charge of the Pool
so I went down to my section.
And there was a tall guy there.
He was looking around,
and then he started running in panic.
I had to catch him.
[♪ exciting music continues playing]
I used to run relay races
in elementary and middle school.
I'm good at running.
[Joonsu panting]
-He got caught.
-He got him.
[both panting]
[grunts]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
They're getting rough.
[gasps]
[both breathing heavily]
[Sanghyun] Joonsu is 194 centimeters tall.
[Joonsu] I was out of breath.
I decided to confront him head on.
[panting]
Physically, I'm quite tall.
I have the edge over most people.
[Sanghyun] Joonsu got a hold of me
and wouldn't let go.
We went around in circles.
I figured I'd get him from this side
with my left hand.
LEE JOONSU LOSES HIS BALANCE
JOONSU'S DESPERATE STRUGGLE
[Joonsu groans]
[both panting heavily]
[patch rips]
[exhales heavily]
[host] Tag confirmed.
SANGHYUN TAGS JOONSU
[panting]
[exhales]
[panting heavily]
He's so strong.
Wow.
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Ddolddol] Either way...
I was going to go straight to the cops
and let myself get caught.
What's going on?
LOOKING AROUND
SPOTS A COP PASS BY FROM AFAR
PRETENDS TO LOOK FOR CLUES
There it is.
[patch rips]
[host] Tag confirmed.
What the heck?
SANGHYUN TAGS DDOLDDOL
[laughing]
-Junseo!
-What the heck?
-[Joonsu] I won't be lonely.
-[Ddolddol groans]
I was right here. Mine was right here.
DDOLDDOL KEEPS UP HIS ACT
[Sanghyun] He clearly knew I was a cop,
but he didn't resist
and let himself get caught.
I wondered why he didn't run away.
That seemed a little suspicious.
[Joonsu] Which team are you on?
-Burglars.
-Me too.
Are you really a Burglar?
Joonsu told me he was a Burglar too.
I thought it was perfect.
I figured I could use him
as my informant. [chuckles]
-Did you see a fan here?
-No.
GOOD CITIZEN APPROACHES WHILE DISGUISED
The fan was right there.
-A big fan?
-Yes.
LEE JOONSU, KIM DDOLDDOL
[host] Tagged players,
please head to prison.
COPS AND ROBBERS ROUND 1
THE GROUNDS
THE POOL
HOTEL BASEMENT
Where is it?
[coughs]
[Jaegyun] I found four in ten minutes.
I was told not to keep looking
beyond that.
I found one more from the photo
and kept its location in mind.
HWANG JAEGYUN CHECKS
ROUND 2 CLUE LOCATIONS IN ADVANCE
FOOTSTEPS ECHO IN THE DISTANCE
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
COP YUK JUNSEO IS IN SEARCH OF CRIMINALS
[♪ fast-paced music playing]
BASEBALL STAR HWANG JAEGYUN
VS UDT YUK JUNSEO
[ZZONE] Someone's running.
Damn it.
HWANG JAEGYUN DROPPED A CLUE
[♪ fast-paced music continues playing]
[panting]
YUK JUNSEO LOSES HWANG JAEGYUN
PICKS UP DROPPED CLUE
[panting]
HWANG JAEGYUN MAKES HIS WAY
UP TO THE GROUNDS
I dropped a clue.
MEANWHILE, PARK JIMIN SEARCHES THE ANNEX
POOL: B3-B1
ANNEX: B2-2F
THE ATMOSPHERE IS TENSE
[Jimin exclaims]
[footsteps approaching]
[♪ exciting music playing]
[Jimin] No!
[yelps]
[host] Tag confirmed.
GOES LOOKING FOR JAEGYUN
WITHOUT CATCHING HIS BREATH
[Jimin] I hadn't found any clues yet,
and I got caught so quickly.
GENERAL CLUES: 0
DECISIVE CLUES: 0
But it is what it is.
I'd rather be in prison early
and focus on figuring out
who the Good Citizens are
and who's the Madman.
That would give me
a better chance of winning.
Because this is an area
where you can put on an act.
PARK JIMIN
[panting]
HWANG JAEGYUN COMES BACK TO THE POOL AREA
[Jaegyun] I couldn't keep
running for long, but I thought
I could get away from them
over short distances.
I was determined to stay away
from the cops for as long as possible.
[Eunsil] Have you been to the Annex?
There should be one or two
down by the Pool.
[Eunsil] The lower level?
-The basement.
-[Junseo] Let's go together.
THE POOL
CASINO: HOTEL B1
POOL: B1
There he is.
[chuckles]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-Let's go.
-[Eunsil] Let's split up.
What the heck?
[Junseo] Jaegyun was so fast
he was already out of my sight.
HWANG JAEGYUN DISAPPEARED
[panting]
YUK JUNSEO KEEPS CHASING HIM
I'm dropping everything.
[groans]
[both panting]
[Jaegyun groans]
-[patch rips]
-Sorry.
[Jaegyun] No worries.
I keep dropping clues.
My goodness.
[host] Tag confirmed.
JUNSEO TAGS JAEGYUN
[Jaegyun] Seeing him run at me was scary.
CURRENT ARREST STATUS
CI: JOONSU, DDOLDDOL
VIOLENT CRIMES: JIMIN, JAEGYUN
THE GROUNDS
[breathing heavily]
There he is.
[♪ fast-paced music playing]
THE ANNEX
HOTEL
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
YANG DAIL HAS DISAPPEARED
[Sanghyun] He was faster than I expected.
I was flustered.
He's not here. Earlier...
THE POOL
By the pool,
I spotted a silhouette,
and it looked like a man.
[♪ sinister music plays]
AS QUIETLY AS POSSIBLE TO NOT BE DETECTED
ENTERING THE POOL AREA
Horseking was there.
HORSEKING IS COLLECTING CLUES
YOUN SANGHYUN CLOSES IN FAST
Isn't he a cop?
I suppose he is.
FULL SPRINT
I'm out of gas.
SANGHYUN IS EXHAUSTED AFTER CHASING DAIL
HORSEKING GETS AWAY EFFORTLESSLY
[panting heavily]
SANGHYUN HEADS THE OPPOSITE WAY
TO WHERE HORSEKING WENT
POOL: B3-B1
ANNEX: B2-2F
THE TWO HEAD TO THE SAME SPOT
LOOKING AROUND
There he is.
[♪ tense music playing]
SEES HIM LATE
YOUN SANGHYUN QUICKLY CATCHES UP
[♪ tense music intensifies]
[both panting]
I grabbed Horseking,
but he was much stronger than I thought.
[Horseking] I've played
a lot of different sports
and especially the ones
that involve physical strength.
I had no fear,
because I could beat anyone.
I will win.
STANDOFF
HORSEKING STARTS TO MOVE
[both grunting]
[Sanghyun] Be careful!
[patch rips]
-[groans] Sorry.
-It's all right.
-Let's go.
-All right.
[host] Tag confirmed.
JUNSEO TAGS HORSEKING
You're so reliable.
[Horseking] I was tagged by Junseo.
I was really caught off guard.
I didn't even get a chance to fight back.
He totally got me.
Our team agreed to call the person
who could help right away.
AN INCOMING CALL
AFTER CATCHING HWANG JAEGYUN
Where are you, Sanghyun?
[Sanghyun] Come back
to where the game started.
Okay.
CHASES HORSEKING WITHOUT TAKING A BREAK
SPOTS HORSEKING
[Junseo] I looked around...
and I knew I had him.
SNEAKING IN
I had to catch him.
[both grunting]
HORSEKING TAGGED IN AN AMBUSH
-Sorry.
-It's all right.
-Let's go.
-All right.
HORSEKING
JUNSEO'S PRISON FILLS UP FIRST
[Jaegyun] Welcome.
-Hello.
Did you find all four?
I did, but I didn't bring them over.
What?
-Why not?
I didn't know I had to.
[Jaegyun] They told us to keep them.
-I thought it was for later.
-[Jaegyun] Really?
So you found clues and left them there?
I left everything there.
You left them where they were?
[Horseking] No, I hid them somewhere else.
He said he hid the clues
and didn't bring them.
He was talking nonsense.
Now, we need to find out
-Assault Criminal 1 and 2.
-Yeah.
Assault Criminal 1, 2, and 3.
Mine doesn't show 1 and 2.
-What?
-It doesn't show, how do I know who's 1?
It doesn't say anything?
-It's not here.
-You're not supposed to show it.
[laughs]
And he was trying to show his card.
He looked like he was totally clueless.
What was that about?
Seriously, I grew increasingly suspicious.
What is he? Is he just a Good Citizen?
Or the Madman?
HORSEKING'S ACTIONS SPARK SUSPICION
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Horseking] Another one got caught?
YOUN SANGHYUN'S PRISON
KIM DDOLDDOL, LEE JOONSU
YUK JUNSEO'S PRISON
PARK JIMIN, HWANG JAEGYUN, HORSEKING
JANG EUNSIL'S PRISON
EMPTY
[Eunsil] I couldn't find my way at first.
I kept getting lost.
The building was huge,
the chase area was massive,
and the pool area was so big
that I couldn't spot anyone.
I think I'm in the wrong place.
Damn it. This is confusing.
I'm lost.
WASTED TIME FROM GETTING LOST
Where's the Annex?
Seriously, I have no idea.
COPS AND ROBBERS ROUND 1
[ZZONE] Interrogation...
Damn it.
ZZONE IS HIDING IN THE POOL AREA
[host] Tag confirmed.
[exclaims]
The Pool?
This one. Coffee. I found that.
[ZZONE] Luckily, in Round 1,
I was able to find
the key clues right away.
From that point on,
I decided to stay hidden.
Of the nine people,
who are the Good Citizens?
Who are the Drug Criminals? Not Jaegyun.
Who got caught? This is driving me crazy.
Jimin...
JOONSU, HORSEKING, DAIL
Jaegyun...
Yang Dail.
THE SOUND OF A PHONE
RINGING SOMEWHERE
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[ringing continues]
Huh?
What?
What is it?
[Sanghyun] Come back
to where the game started.
Come over there? Okay.
Okay. Okay, got it.
[whispers] The Pool is too dangerous.
This is driving me crazy.
As for Jimin...
I'm not sure if I can trust her.
This is nuts.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
What the heck? Hold on! What the heck?
[♪ exciting music playing]
Hold on! What the heck?
[ZZONE screams]
Help!
[screams]
Get out of the pool!
[patch rips]
[groans disappointedly]
[host] Tag confirmed.
EUNSIL TAGS ZZONE
-Let's go.
-[ZZONE] I should've hidden.
Why did I not notice?
Something felt off. I went to the Pool...
and it felt like someone was hiding
and watching me from behind a pillar.
I spotted ZZONE.
I saw her shadow,
and I figured it was the perfect spot
to trick someone.
So I went around and caught her.
JANG EUNSIL
Hold on! What the heck?
I'm the first one here. Thank you.
[exhales]
JANG EUNSIL'S PRISON
ZZONE
Thank you.
REMAINING TIME
HOTEL MAIN ENTRANCE
GENERAL CLUES: 3
DECISIVE CLUES: 0
Damn it, where are my clues?
5 MINUTES LEFT
YANG DAIL'S LOOKING FOR THE LAST CLUE
HOTEL REAR ENTRANCE
[Jieun] Is this a dead end?
GENERAL CLUES: 3
DECISIVE CLUES: 1
ALL CLUES SECURED
ENTERING THE HOTEL TO FIND A SPOT TO HIDE
[♪ fast-paced music playing]
Damn it!
[Sanghyun] Who's missing?
YOUN SANGHYUN WAS NEARBY
Shin Jieun!
Dail, run!
Run!
Where do I go?
[shouts]
[exclaims frustratedly]
JANG EUNSIL CLOSES IN FAST
DID HE GET AWAY?
HERE COMES YUK JUNSEO
[footsteps]
[Dail] I thought I got away
and went outside.
HERE COMES YOUN SANGHYUN
[sighs]
That's when I got really competitive,
and I had to catch him.
Dail!
[patch rips]
[exhales]
[host] Tag confirmed.
[sighs] Just my luck.
SHIN JIEUN AND YANG DAIL WERE TAGGED
4 MINUTES TO GO
Who's left now? Did we get Jimin?
-No, not yet.
-I'll call HQ.
-[Junseo] Who?
-Jimin. This person.
-We got her.
-Really?
There's someone else.
-Did we get everyone?
-Pani Bottle.
Yeah, he's still out there.
If one more person's caught, it's over.
[sighs heavily]
The cop selections were bad.
Pani Bottle should've been a cop.
Then, we could've run away forever.
If I were a cop, I wouldn't have caught
a single person.
It's going to be over soon.
There's about three minutes left.
REMAINING TIME
-Call HQ.
-Okay.
Please tell us Pani Bottle's location.
COPS ARE ALLOWED TO LOOK UP
A CRIMINAL'S LOCATION ONCE PER ROUND
[phone rings]
-The Grounds.
-[Junseo] Okay.
[Sanghyun] We'll find him soon
if he's at the Grounds.
[Junseo] I wanted to track down
every last one of them.
-You check this side.
-Sure, this side?
Yeah, outside.
-Eunsil, check over there. I'll go here.
-Okay.
I will find him.
Pani Bottle...
A FRANTIC SEARCH BEFORE TIME RUNS OUT
[Eunsil] I feel like he's hiding.
Where is he?
He must be hiding somewhere strange.
[host] Two minutes remaining.
SNOW REMOVAL SUPPLIES
[objects rattle]
[Pani Bottle]
God, just stay the fuck away.
Why do you keep coming?
I had to find four clues in Round 1.
I had found three.
I needed to find one more.
I saw a snow removal supply box
in the photo.
It was exactly my size.
It was like a cozy studio apartment.
So I stayed there and waited it out.
I figured as long as I hold out,
I could survive Round 1
without being interrogated.
[Sanghyun] Has Pani Bottle vanished?
I couldn't possibly find Pani Bottle.
I didn't see him.
[Sanghyun] I knew he was at the Grounds,
but I didn't know exactly where.
[Junseo] Time's running out. Let's run.
[Sanghyun] He's at the Grounds?
The Grounds?
He's at the Grounds?
-That's impossible.
-[Junseo] Go in there.
All three of us
should've looked for him together.
But I think it was too late.
How could he be at the Grounds?
[Eunsil] We didn't know where he was.
Time was running short.
[Sanghyun] So I felt a lot of pressure.
[Junseo] Pani Bottle was nowhere in sight.
Even so, we didn't give up until the end.
REMAINING TIME
I was like, "Uh-oh!"
[Pani Bottle breathing nervously]
[♪ tense music playing]
I felt like I'd get caught
if I moved even a little bit.
It was as if I was someone
hiding among the dead
in World War II.
If they found me, I'd get shot.
I stayed absolutely still.
[footsteps approaching]
REMAINING TIME
[clock ticking]
[buzzer sounds]
[host] Round 1's chase is over.
All surviving criminals,
please gather in the Main Hall.
ROUND 1'S CHASE HAS ENDED
"Surviving criminals,
go to the Main Hall."
How many survived then?
[Joonsu] Just one, right?
Is it only Pani Bottle?
How did he pull it off?
I thought he'd be the easiest to catch.
SNOW REMOVAL SUPPLIES
[exhales]
[exclaims]
Time's dragging on like hell.
[groans]
[sighs]
-Mr. Pani Bottle.
-Yes?
You are the only criminal who survived.
I see.
Please put every clue you found
on the table.
MISSION REWARD: SURVIVORS
CAN DESTROY ALL OF THEIR CLUES
[dealer] I'll examine the clues.
You found a handkerchief,
cotton gloves, energy gum,
and a designer bag.
[Pani Bottle] Right.
The designer bag is an incorrect clue.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[Pani Bottle] But it was here.
What the heck?
Can you double-check your profile card?
CLUES
OCT 22, 2025
JOB: CAR KEYS, GUM, GLOVES
CRIME: RECEIPT, HANDKERCHIEF, DEAD PHONE
OF NOTE: EARPLUGS, DECAF COFFEE,
BOTTLE OF SLEEPING PILLS
I checked the profile card,
and it said nothing about designer bags.
But I found the clue here.
[dealer] It has nothing to do with you.
[Pani Bottle] There were supposed
to be earplugs, but I couldn't find them.
Are there two snow removal supply boxes?
24 MINUTES BEFORE PANI BOTTLE CAME
HORSEKING HID HIS CLUE
IN THE SNOW REMOVAL SUPPLY BOX
Let's look outside.
[mumbling]
I can't stop thinking about
those three clues I left.
It's driving me crazy.
You can go find them all next round.
You can find five.
I found it in the box.
CONFUSED BY HORSEKING
They should've been earplugs.
[dealer] The designer bag
is an incorrect clue.
Since you brought an incorrect clue,
three will be revealed to all
as a penalty.
We'll dispose of the remaining clues.
Please return to the Main Hall.
How did this happen?
[Pani Bottle] That's when I realized
it was someone else's,
and I was missing something.
At that moment,
I was out of it and couldn't move,
so I never really checked it.
I couldn't risk getting caught.
That's when I knew something was wrong.
[host] All cops,
please go to your interrogation rooms.
-We caught a lot.
-Right.
-Save for one, we got them all.
-[Sanghyun] Yeah.
Seriously...
I underestimated the cops.
I can't survive Round 2.
If I get caught in Round 2, isn't it over?
-We have to survive 70 minutes in Round 2.
-[Jieun] What should we do?
At this point,
the cops have the upper hand...
because they're taking key clues
from each of us.
One each from the nine of us.
If we're the criminals...
then the only way we can win
is by identifying
the Good Citizens or the Madman.
We already got caught,
so we can't help that.
If we find the Good Citizens
or the Madman, we'll win.
Yeah, we need to identify them.
But we don't know who they are.
[Jimin] I think
we should at least do that.
We should find the Good Citizens.
Should we pretend to be Good Citizens
in front of the cops?
[Jieun] Yeah.
-[Junseo] Hello.
-[Jaegyun] Are you here to let us out?
I need to interrogate you.
[all exclaim]
[Sanghyun] It's only 10 minutes.
Interrogation time.
[Ddolddol] I tried so hard to find clues.
[Horseking] This is so unfair.
[ZZONE chuckles] This is crazy.
[♪ unsettling music playing]
INTERROGATION ROOM
[Dail] I think we can confuse them
with our words
to mislead them enough
and hide what crime we committed.
I'm...
a terrible liar, and it shows.
[Dail] This isn't going to be easy.
GULP
[Jieun] I'll try to stay quiet
as much as possible.
[Junseo] I tried to come up with questions
that would put them under pressure
during the interrogation.
[Eunsil] From the moment
I entered the interrogation room,
I felt intimidated by the atmosphere.
So I decided to keep things
as serious as possible.
What's your nationality?
I'm from...
Heaven.
I'm an Angel.
I'm mixed race.
I'm half Heaven and half Korean.
[snorts]
-You're quite unique.
-[ZZONE chuckles]
Was there any murder weapon you used?
-It's a secret.
-[Junseo] A secret?
You've chosen
to say as little as possible, haven't you?
-[Jaegyun] Of course.
-Hmm...
It'll be tough.
No one's going to say anything.
How old are you?
I'm in my thirties.
-[Sanghyun] In your thirties?
-I'm a woman.
-A woman in her thirties?
-[Ddolddol] Yes.
I'm a witch.
[Sanghyun] A witch?
Is he serious?
Or is he joking? I wasn't sure.
Hold on.
-I need to check something.
-[Ddolddol] Sure.
You're supposed to submit
your clues to me.
CAUGHT CRIMINALS MUST GIVE
A GENERAL AND DECISIVE CLUE
Here are the clues.
GIVES CLUES RIGHT AWAY
[Sanghyun] He took out the clues,
and I was a little thrown off.
Is this right?
-Write it down fast.
-Sure, thirties...
I'm here to help you out.
-Is that so?
-An alcoholic.
WHO'S THE COP?
"An alcoholic."
A high heel to the manager's head...
You hit the manager
in the head with a high heel?
Yes, I took his valuables.
THE WITCH ADMITS HER CRIME
Is it okay to spill everything like this?
-Sure, I'm a Good Citizen.
-[Sanghyun] "A Good Citizen."
What?
What was that?
I think I was a little flustered.
Kim Ddolddol
was trying to prove then
that he was a Good Citizen.
You know what Joonsu will say?
He's a nurse...
-And what else?
-[Sanghyun] Joonsu is Burglar 3
and had an e-cigarette.
When Joonsu came in,
I compared that with Joonsu's clues.
Evidence.
You mean the clues?
Here you go.
[Sanghyun] Joonsu brought an e-cigarette
and a liquid cartridge.
It was exactly what he said.
I was able to catch
both Ddolddol and Joonsu.
I think Ddolddol was a huge help.
[footsteps approaching]
SOMEONE ARRIVES AT THE INTERROGATION ROOM
[knocks on door]
Come in.
Hello.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[distorted voice]
Did you catch all the Drug Criminals?
[Eunsil] We're working on it.
[distorted voice]
Aren't they Jimin and ZZONE?
This is all I can tell you.
[Junseo] Any info
about the other suspects?
[distorted voice]
I know a few things, including that.
I'll make it simple for you.
[Sanghyun] Are you a Good Citizen?
[distorted voice] Yes.
[♪ soft, eerie music playing]
Translated by Youji Kim